(wind eerily gusting)
(sinister music)
(sinister music builds)
(thudding)
(gasping)
(thudding continues)
(shallow breathing)
(loud screaming)
Uh... Ah.
(screaming)
Ah...
(grunting)
(shouting in Gaelic)
(sinister music builds)
(screaming)
Ah! Ah...
(head cracking, squelching)
(loud screaming)
(gasping)
Uh! Ah!
(cracking, squelching)
(loud screaming)
Uh! Uh...
Uh!
(slicing)
Uh...
(thud)
(choking)
(blood spluttering)
(thud)
(gasping)
(blade clinks)
(blood squelching)
(foreboding music)
(gasping)
Aaargh! Aaargh!
Aaaaaargh!
(pop music)
♪ Kissed someone at a party ♪
Apparently, they...
-Okay, guys.
Smile.
(phone recording tone beeps)
Sixty-second style critique,
and go.
Hoodie wants to party like
its 1999, and so does the boy.
And what hasn't
already been said
by thousands
of adoring followers?
Trench coat's on point,
just like the bod in it.
Influencer queen styling
the season for us.
Now what do we have? Oh.
-Oh, come on, dude.
Driving on the wrong
side of the road. Distractions.
Come on.
-Sure.
Well, don't we love
a man of focus?
Hmm, yeah.
Check shirt is saying
macho lumberjack.
But the turn up on
the skinny jeans are saying,
'Gimme Kombucha, baby!'
-Sean, fuck off.
Mixed signals are so in.
What about these two?
-Sean?
-It's fine.
-Oh, right, yeah.
-No, delete it, yeah?
-It's fine.
Alright, yeah.
Sorry, Orla.
-It's okay.
I'll edit you out.
No, Seanie, delete it!
Fuck's sake, I look
just fucking purged.
Right, it's been hours, yeah?
Oh, fuck off, Lorcan.
I can still uninvite you.
Sean? Delete.
Sure thing, Ness!
(light background music)
-You okay, babe?
-Satnav: Continue straight.
Arriving at your destination
in one minute.
Yes, yes, yes.
Destination will be
on the left.
-Sean: Are we there?
-Austin: I think so.
Can I get a drum roll, please?
(mimics drum roll)
Ooh, and let the weekend begin.
Okay. Quiet, guys.
(phone recording tone beeps)
So, I told you guys last week
that I was finally taking
my posse on a lil' vacay.
-Nessa: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-Austin: What?
-Austin, go slower!
-Oh.
-I'm trying to film it!
-Sorry, babe.
Here, I'll back up.
You want to do it again?
What are you thinking?
You know I need to film.
Oh, sorry.
I'll back up. Park again.
Don't. It's fine. We're parked.
-No, I'll back up...
-We're parked!
I'll do it inside.
Babe. (chuckles)
I just want it to be perfect.
I'll make it up to you later.
Yeah?
Sean: Eww, company, people.
(chuckles) Let's go, guys!
Come on, Seanie.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold up.
-Wait till you see inside.
-Let me get my camera.
Oh, whoa!
Come on, let's get you changed.
They don't even have
the door open.
You coming?
Yeah, in a minute.
(background chatter)
(van door slides open)
(knocking)
Where the fuck is she?
Try it again, Ness. No F-bombs.
Did you check for a lock box?
Lorcan, sweetie,
there is no lock box.
There is no phone number.
Said she'd meet us here.
(car approaching)
-Austin: Yo, look, she's here.
-About time.
You're early!
We're excited.
So...no problem finding it then?
(shutter clicks)
Sorry, this is just
for my channel.
That's cool, right?
-No. No problem.
Uh, the phone actually took us
straight here,
surprisingly, so...
Well, there's not
much to it now, but...
this place used to be the most
magnificent estate.
But the big house burnt down,
and sure, that put
an end to that.
Sean: Do you own the place?
Or...
Nora: Oh, God, no.
I just hold the keys.
(background chatter)
(suspenseful music)
(thuds)
Jesus!...
(background chatter)
He hasn't even been here.
Oh, listen to me.
I'm droning on.
You didn't come here
for a history lesson.
Enjoy your visit.
And if there's anything
at all you need,
I'm just below down
there in the farmhouse
just before the main road.
The number is there
on the table.
So, I'll go.
-(saying goodbye)
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, of course.
(car engine starting)
Well...
let me introduce you all to
the hard-earned fruit
of my labour.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for asking me along.
Come on, guys, I'm not doing
it for gratitude.
Keep it up.
Austin: Oooh! Wow. My god.
It's super cute, right?
Oh, snap...you weren't kidding.
This is sweet, Ness.
Nessa: I told you guys
you'd like it.
Austin: Oh, Ness, you nailed it.
Whoa, nice.
Nessa: The light
is perfect, right?
Austin: The light, ah...
I want to do some filming here.
-Austin: Cool.
Nessa: Wait, wait. No.
(muffled chatter)
How many bedrooms?
Nessa: Stay out of the master,
Seanie!
I've got a dibs.
Austin: Let's see what
we can do in here first,
and I'm gonna go
making plan now.
Nessa: Thank you.
Austin: Okay?
See the flowers?
Yeah.
Seanie, I need some tags.
Sean: That was okay?
(muffled chatter)
(music becomes distorted)
(crows cawing)
(ominous music)
Austin: So, get the lighting in
and then...
Oh, we're gonna use
this table, I think.
Have the Nessentials on there.
We might take a couple
photos over there.
Can you help me move
this table for the shoot?
Sure. I mean, it doesn't
look heavy, so...
Okay. Um...
I'm gonna get my gear in here.
Alright.
I'll get the bags.
I'm gonna be back in a minute.
(door closes)
Nessa: Seanie, go help him.
(phone beeps)
So, I told you guys
I was going to shoot my posse
for a lil' vacay.
(faint eerie whispers)
(suspenseful music)
(eerie whispers intensify)
(trees creaking)
(sinister music)
(eerie whispers continue)
-(gasps)
-Boujee, right?
(chuckles)
When I saw the listing online,
I knew it was perfect.
And it's peaceful.
I thought it'd be good
for you to...
get away and...
Sorry. (sighs)
I just know what
you can achieve.
Just have to be brave.
Austin has almost a million
subscribers on YouTube,
and his Insta's lit up.
I think I can finally break
the U.S. with this push.
I bet you will.
(background chatter)
Thanks. (chuckles)
Kinda have to.
-Where's this stuff going?
I don't know, man. I'll ask her.
Where, babe?
Kitchen counter, boys!
Come on, this way.
It's okay I invited him, right?
'Bleisure' trip.
(chuckles) Business,
leisure - bleisure.
(laughter)
Phone: One saved message.
One year ago.
(phone beeps)
Fiona: Orla, I need you
back home.
You knew what your father
would be like
if we don't leave on time.
Ciara: Hurry up
so we can go camping,
big shit-ster!
-Ciara?!
(end-of-message tone)
(sinister music)
(sighs)
(flashback) Fiona: Orla?
Gareth: That's it.
I'm stopping the car.
-Gareth, watch the road.
- Ciara: I just wanted to see.
Orla: Never touch
my phone again.
(horn honks, vehicles crashing)
(eerie faint whispers)
(sinister music)
(high tempo music)
♪ All gold teeth,
I like my girls like that ♪
♪ Never smilin',
♪ Dirty ass knees,
I like my girls like that ♪
♪ I like my girls like that,
♪ Never dancing,
I like my girls like that ♪
♪ Never in pink,
♪ Lay it on thick,
I like my girls like that ♪
♪ I like my girls like that,
♪ Don't wanna see or hear
nobody else so ♪
♪ All that she needs is her
hand and herself ♪
♪ Pretty ugly,
I want my girls like that ♪
Alright, influencer queen
on her throne.
Don't cha know it?
Uh, dude, can you dial up
the light for me?
-Sean: Sure thing.
-Thank you.
Yeah. A little bit more. Yeah.
(shutter clicks)
And I got it. Nice work.
-Hey now.
-What?
Seanie's only meant to do
what I tell him to do.
(camera clicks)
You have to brand him
like the Romans.
The Romans used to brand
their workers.
Not just a pretty face.
I also studied history.
(camera clicking)
Well, I dropped out.
But I got in.
(light music)
Austin: Just go ahead and smile.
(camera clicks)
Nice. Hold it. Hold it.
(muffled chatter)
(sighs) So...
she's still getting changed?
Mm-hmm.
And the...you know?
Yeah, it's been
a few weeks, so...
But they...they're just
cuts, right?
She wouldn't, like...go further?
I don't know, man.
I just hope this works.
You know, it's been
a year and...
It'll work.
Ness knows what she's doing.
-Is this stuff any good?
-No, no, no, no, don't.
Okay. She only had
a few samples made.
She needs all of them
for the photos.
She's put everything
into this thing but...
nobody wants to stock them.
Her dad had to pay
for these new ones.
Like, he thinks she's using it
to pay for a business course.
So, if she can't make
this work...
then donezo.
(door closes)
Austin: Where's she going?
(mysterious music)
We should all go
with her, right?
We could. Sure.
Well, I can bring my camera.
We were gonna get some
outdoor shots anyway.
Now that is a plan.
(mysterious music intensifies)
(eerie whispering)
Hey, you bailing on us?
Just wanted some air.
Photo op!
(camera clicks)
-Gotcha.
-Okay. (giggling)
(ominous music)
(birds twittering)
(eerie whispering)
So, things are moving
pretty fast with Ness.
Hm. Only way I know how.
Sounds like true love.
Yo...
Yo, what's the deal with Orla?
Ness said she was...um,
depressed or something, but...
I swear I've seen her before.
-Wait...Ness didn't tell you?
-No.
Everyone's seen Orla before.
A year ago, her Insta
was insane.
But then... (sighs deeply)
Okay. And you're gonna tell me?
I can't spill tea but...
these days Orla's basically
like, you know,
dead girl walking.
I don't think she's in the mood.
Jesus, Lorcan.
Isn't her mood the problem?
-Hm.
She can't keep going on like
this, which is nowhere.
You're not gonna be the hero
who's gonna save her.
She's got to wise up
and do it herself.
Yeah.
(whispers) We talked about this.
She's got no choice,
and you know I'm right.
Stick to the plan.
-Hey, where is Orla going?
-What?
Oh, shit!
(eerie music)
-Lorcan: Orla?
-Nessa: Orla?
Austin: Man, you see this stuff?
Looks like someone hung it up.
-Nessa: It's so weird.
Austin: Creep fest.
Oh, man.
What the hell is this place?
Sean: Portal dolmen.
A Celtic tomb.
Austin: What, Celtic
as in ancient?
Lorcan: How did you find it?
Thought I heard something.
This is amazing! (chuckles)
Yeah. This, uh...this will work.
Whoa, it's so nice.
Wow.
Oh, my god, it's so Irish.
Let's get a picture up there.
-Yeah, go around, go around.
-Oh, sorry.
Sean, do you mind helping me up?
It's a shame you don't have
your products. Oh, my God.
Lorcan: Dude, I wonder
who built these.
Austin: I have no idea, man,
but it's sick.
Okay, does this look good?
Austin: That is perfect.
-Okay. Hair? Fine?
-Hair is perfect.
(camera clicks)
Good.
Give me some poses. Awesome.
Nice. Nessentials on three.
One, two, three...
-Nessential!
(laughs)
Austin: Let's come back
with different outfits.
Look. There's something on it.
Lorcan: Dearg...
Due. Wait, what is that?
Dearg Due.
It is Irish, so it is.
Yeah. But what does it mean?
I dunno, so I don't.
'Red'...something.
(eerie whispering)
(sinister music)
(eerie whispering intensifies)
(whispering grows even louder)
(rhythmic drum beat)
Orla?
Nessa: Got it?
Austin: Nice. Hair...just push.
-(Nessa giggles)
-Beautiful.
Do you promise I look alright
from up here?
-Wonderful.
-Okay. Thank you.
(camera clicks)
Austin: Back a little.
Step back a little.
-Like this?
-Oh, shit! (screams)
-Austin: No, no, no. Ness!
(loud thud)
(ominous music)
No. No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
-Woah, what's going on?
-No! (sobs)
Orla? What happened? Hey?
-What's going on?
-Hey, it's okay.
What's up?
-Austin: Dude, what happened?
Okay. Is she okay?
You were just...you were...
Sean: Are you all right, Orla?
Lorcan, it's getting
kind of dark,
maybe we should...
Yeah, let's get back, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Let's...
let's get you back.
(Orla' panicked breathing)
Babe, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
We'll come back tomorrow
or something.
Oh, you're freezing, babe.
Lorcan: It's okay, babe.
It's not far.
(sinister music)
(gurgling, bubbling)
(night bird chirps)
(upbeat background music)
♪ It's been some time since
I felt the fear ♪
♪ This feels like it... ♪
-It's in the oven.
30 minutes, people.
Are you left-handed?
-Nope. But I eat southpaw.
It's weird, huh?
-Nessa: I don't.
-Lorcan: Oh, shit.
-(Nessa laughs)
♪ This time I won't
self sabotage ♪
♪ I can't go back to... ♪
-Show me, babe.
More.
I'm selling miracles.
My body miraculous.
(pot bubbling)
(ominous music)
(thuds)
(gasps)
The Dearg Due...
the first vampire ever recorded
in western culture.
Thought to be
the only real vampire
that has ever walked the earth.
-What?
-Come on.
The name in the woods.
Googled it.
Legend says the Dearg Due
was a fallen angel,
an immortal entity of darkness
that needed a willing human host
to survive in our world.
It first bound itself with
the body of a Celtic warrior,
luring peasants to it with
its powers of mind control...
-Austin: That's wild, dude.
- ...before using fangs
to feast on their blood.
The blood sustained the
warrior's unnatural flesh
for hundreds of years,
until the warrior's body
finally grew too weak.
And so, the Dearg Due
found a new host.
And another.
Moving from one human body
to the next...
for centuries.
-Austin: Wooo!
The only way to stop
the Dearg Due
was to bury it headfirst in
a grave covered with stones
and surrounded
by hawthorn bushes.
But this would only imprison
it in the soil.
Austin: (laughs) This is crazy.
The Dearg Due
can never be killed.
And anyone who strays too close
to where it lies
puts themselves within reach
of its dark powers.
Make no mistake, the Dearg Due
will return!
(laughter)
Wait, uh...
(door opens)
Dude, what are you doing?
You're freaking her out!
Fuck's sake, it's a myth.
That means it isn't real.
You're welcome.
(eerie rumbling)
(crickets chirping)
(faint whispers, gurgling)
(upbeat background
music continues)
(keys tapping)
(phone pings)
Oh, three days.
They say they have Wi-Fi though,
so follow me for hijinks!
(phone pings again)
Oh, have you ever camped,
ricky-five-oh?
It's gonna be cheugy as fuck.
-Ciara: Orla said fuck!
-Fiona: Orla!
My little shit-ster. Ciara!
I look silly. Give it to me!
- Fiona: That's enough.
- Orla: Mum!
Mum, I'm live, give it back!
- Fiona: This is family time.
Just turn it off.
-Mum, give it to me! Please.
-Fiona: Orla!
Gareth: That's it.
I'm stopping the car.
(gravel crunches)
Gareth, watch the road.
Ciara: I just wanted to see.
Orla: Never touch
my phone again!
(truck horn honks)
(loud crash, screaming)
Oh.
(eerie whispering, gurgling)
(sinister music)
(lights flickering)
(choking)
(coughs, struggles to breathe)
(heavy breathing)
(gagging)
(coughing)
(panicked breathing)
(panicked breathing continues)
(low, eerie rumbling)
(eerie music)
(screams)
What's going on?
Orla?
Can we just eat, yeah?
(dark music)
(snarling, growling)
(bird screeching)
(birds screech)
(trees creaking)
(clock ticking)
(distorted talking)
Um, yeah, just kind of kept
posting and posting, posting.
The more I posted,
the more followers I'd get.
And then one day, it just kind
of blew up.
Oh. And you just
film everything?
Yeah. I mean, it...it's all just
following the algorithm.
You know, you just gotta upload
every single day.
People, once they subscribe,
they'll...
they'll pretty much
watch anything, so...
-Hmm.
-And he's gonna hit a million,
which is when the ad payouts
get really big.
Influence is power. Right, Ness?
And money, Sean. Money.
Austin: Well, I just went all in
from the start.
(distorted) You know, got a loan
from my parents...
(fades out)
(eerie whispering)
(sinister music)
(glass shatters)
Lorcan: Whoa.
-Orla; Shit, sorry.
-It's okay.
It's okay, babe.
It isn't.
I'm not...
(deep sigh)
Sorry.
It's nothing.
We're just worried about you.
-You think I'm going crazy.
-No. Not at all.
We just think that you're stuck,
and it's getting to your head.
(foreboding music)
(snarling)
I've been watching you
like this for a year.
We...wanted you to come here
so we can talk
about this and fix it.
Is this an intervention?
You're my best friend.
And I wanted to help you.
And at some point, you're gonna
have to start
making some real money.
And you already know how.
I mean, before...
you know...
you were fire.
I mean, I know you didn't
break out or anything,
but people will remember you
for sure.
My God.
You don't worry about setting up
your socials or anything.
You can just start on mine
and just start rising slowly.
Austin's brought all
of his equipment.
I have the whole wardrobe
with me.
I even brought a foundation
shade that suits your tone...
(sinister music)
(distorted chatter)
(eerie breathing)
(rustling)
You're low-key famous, babe.
The collabs would slap!
Are you fucking...serious?
You want me back
influencing with you?
Because it would help you!
No, you don't wanna help me.
You wanna cash in on me.
You want me to help you sell
your bullshit pills!
-Bullshit?! What the fuck?
-It's not real, Ness!
-What the fuck?
-It's all fake!
The filters. The likes.
The photoshop. The fucking diet
pills from China.
Oh, my God.
So, it's like that now.
You're real and wise
just because...
Because I died...Ness!
They cut a hole in my throat
and shoved a tube into my lungs
to force me to breathe.
(dramatic music)
If you're so much better
than us, show us your arms.
-Lorcan: Ness, don't.
-Austin: Holy shit, Ness!
If you're so wise
and you don't need help,
then why the fuck are you
cutting yourself?
Lorcan: Ness, come on. Leave it.
Because all I want
is my family back.
But they're gone...
and it's my fault.
You know it is.
And I wish the doctors
had left me dead.
I wish I could be
with them again.
And I tried.
I did.
But then I thought about
what it was like...
when I was gone.
There was nothing.
Just...darkness.
So, I was too much of a little
bitch to go through with it.
Irony, right?
I want to be dead,
but I'm too scared to die.
So, I'm fucked.
And you can't help me.
Nothing can.
Hey, babe. Babe, wait!
-Austin: What the hell was that?
-Lorcan: Orla?
-Babe?
-Did you know?
Babe, she's drunk. She doesn't
know what she's saying.
She hasn't had any carbs.
And she slammed a whole bottle.
-Did you know?
Lorcan: It's been a year.
We have to try something.
I can't keep watching
you like this.
It's eating you up inside.
Ness is right.
Ness is right, you're famous.
If you just got back online...
(sinister music)
(exhales)
Why didn't you tell me?
You said she needed
lifting up, not this.
So, it turns out my best friend
thinks I'm full
of fucking bullshit!
(wind whistles)
You know what?
Maybe she's right.
Wanna see?
(whispers) Ssh...Photoshop.
What else?
My revitalising blend...
it's a multivitamin.
And the diet pills are diuretics
from Wuhan.
It's all fake.
Austin: Ness.
It's all bullshit.
And you can FUCKING SUE ME!
(wind whistles)
I'm just doing
what I have to do.
I must be fucked
like everyone else.
You've got to take risks
and do whatever it takes.
There is no other choice.
And Orla's gonna
have to accept that,
whether she knows it yet or not.
(recording end tone beeps)
(phone thud)
(sniffs)
I think it would be a really...
a really bad idea to post that.
I think you're right.
(wind picks up)
(suspenseful music)
Nessa: What the fuck?!
Lorcan: It's okay,
it's just the power.
-I saw candles earlier.
-I don't have a phone signal.
Sean: Wi-Fi's down, Ness.
There's no signal out here.
Lorcan: Because
there's no electricity.
Nessa: Don't have any signal.
How the fuck am I going to post?
Austin: Come on, Ness.
(muffled chatter)
(chatter becomes distorted)
(sinister music)
(ominous music fades in)
Nessa: Everyone will be posting
all weekend.
If I can't post, I'm fucked!
(jump scare)
(screaming)
Lorcan: Orla?
Guys, guys, look.
-Oh, my God!
-What the hell?
Is she naked?
(moaning softly)
Jesus.
What the fuck are you doing?
(sinister music)
What is it? Hey?
Hey, what is it?
-Ugh...
-The lights, Austin,
the lights, I think
they're too bright.
Austin: Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
(machine beeps)
Okay, they're off.
It's okay. You can come in.
(foreboding music)
You're bringing her inside?
This is completely insane.
What the hell are you doing?
You don't even know who she is.
Austin: Oh, my God.
Lorcan: Dude, seriously?
You're right. Sorry.
Who the fuck is she?
Sean: I don't think this is
a good idea, guys.
Holy shit. Look at her.
(squelching)
Ugh. She stinks.
It's okay. You hear me?
You're safe.
-Do you think she's escaped?
-What?
From a serial killer
or something.
There's no serial killer.
Well, she didn't do
this to herself.
This is wild, guys.
(heavy breathing)
(rising ominous music)
Get the fuck away
from my friend!
-(snarls)
-Lorcan: Ness!
-Austin: Go, grab her.
-Lorcan: I'm trying.
-Nessa: Get away from me!
-Lorcan: Hey, hey, hey!
Get the door, get the door!
Austin: Lorcan, get her!
(screams)
The bathroom, we can lock
her in. Get the key!
(chaotic high tempo music)
(grunts)
Agh...
(key turns)
(heavy breathing)
-Urgh. Oh my God.
-Holy shit.
-Are...are you okay, Ness?
-Did you see that?
She tried to bite me...
in my fucking face.
I'm going to bed.
I want that crazy bitch gone.
I mean it.
-Here, I'll get that for you.
-I know how to do it.
-Okay.
(dramatic music)
Did she hurt you?
Hey, we gotta...
we gotta do something.
-We need the po-po. For real.
-No, we, we can't.
The po-po, they don't
have phones.
I didn't drink, so I can drive.
The woman who gave us the keys,
she said she lives close, right?
So, she might have
a working landline.
Guys, we need to get
our shit together.
She's locked in there,
so nobody open the door
until I get the guards here.
(chatter fades out)
Alright?
You'll be alright, yeah?
I'll be back soon
as I can, okay?
I'll get going.
(sinister music)
Guess we're cleaning this up.
(car engine starting)
(car rumbles distantly)
(girl gasping
and breathing rapidly)
(ominous music)
(rhythmic breathing)
(flickering)
(rhythmic breathing continues)
(dark music)
(high pitched ringing)
Nessa: What the fuck, Sean?
Why is this place still a mess?
I'm sorry. My head is...
No, you're always sorry.
Sorry little Sean.
Apologising for everything.
My head hurts, Ness.
You're supposed
to work for me, you know?
You work for me,
you learn from me,
which means you should
clean up this mess.
I let you put me
in your shitty videos.
Am I not gonna get anything back
from that?
Why are you being mean?
Because I'm sick of this.
I need you to prove
you're loyal to me
or I'm done with you.
Ness. I...
I'm loyal.
Prove it.
How?
You know how.
(foreboding music)
(whispers) Pick it up.
-Um...
-(screams) Pick it up!
Mark yourself.
Like the Romans did.
Prove you're mine.
(ominous music)
Like the Romans did.
Remember?
(snivels)
(laughs, scoffs) You are...
so pathetic.
If you don't do this,
I'm done with you.
You can go back to being
a nobody in Churchtown.
Queen of fucking nowhere.
(laughs)
(panicked breathing)
You're a follower, Sean.
(eerie whispering)
You'll always need someone
stronger than you
telling you what to do.
If you lose me,
you lose everything.
(sobs)
(screams) Do it!
Come on, Seanie.
Just a little mark.
(chaotic, discordant music)
Sean!
(growling)
Nessa: Sean! Sean!
Where is she?
(knife drops)
(footsteps approaching)
What the hell happened?
-Who?
-Ness. She was just here!
I've been out there
the whole time.
She hasn't come out
of the bedroom.
She was here!
She was right there.
(panting)
(car rumbling)
(tyres screeching)
(car horn honks)
Hello? Anybody?
(car door closes)
Hello?
-This is private property.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
You let us into the house today.
Oh...oh, it's you.
Jesus. You put the fear
of God in me.
Sorry.
We, we had a...
There's, there's been...sorry.
It's been a lot.
I need to call the police.
The police?
Why, what's happened? Is...
Is...is somebody hurt?
I have a first aid kit.
No. There's a woman
in the house.
We...we found her outside.
-Where did she come from?
-I don't know.
I, I think she crawled through
the woods or something,
but we had no signal,
and I was wondering
if you had a landline?
What, you think just because
I live in this old dump,
I still have a landline?
-No, no. I...I just...
-Of course I do.
Go on.
Oh, God! (hard clang)
-Aah!
(slumps to the ground)
(sighs)
Come on!
(frightening breathing)
(crashing)
(phone beeps)
Yes!
(eerie whispering)
Nessa: What else?
My revitalising blend...
No.
...it's a multivitamin.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
You might not lose the fat,
but you'll shit your guts out
to fit into the dress you love.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
It's all fake.
It's all bullshit.
It's over.
And you can fucking sue me!
I didn't post it.
Doing what I have to do...
Doing what I have to do.
I must be fucked
ike everyone else.
No. No. No. No...
(rising discordant music)
Here, dude.
It's okay.
Just chill.
(heavy breathing)
(glass shatters)
(sinister music)
(exhales sharply)
You better stay put, lady.
Babe? Did you hear
something break?
Is that you?
(knocks) I know you're pissed.
Okay? We couldn't just leave her
out there,
but Lorcan's gone to get help.
We'll get her out of here soon.
(eerie whispering)
(dramatic music)
(dark music)
Okay, I'm gonna come in, okay?
Wow.
I promised I'd make
it up to you.
-Yeah, okay.
-(giggles)
(dark music)
I haven't had as much
to drink as you.
Sshhhhhhhhhhhh...
(dark music intensifies)
(whispers) What the...?
No.
No way!
(intense kissing)
(ominous music)
(gurgling)
Fuck!
(panicked breathing)
(kissing continues)
Orla?
It's out.
(chaotic music)
(squelching)
Get your camera.
Really?
(phone pings)
(suspenseful music)
(fearful music)
Jesus Christ, what the fuck!
(bones creaking)
Hey! Hey!
Austin?
No. No, no, no, no!
What are you?
(scoffs)
(horrifying music)
(fearful breathing)
(heart beating)
(slow breathing)
(heart continues beating)
(growls)
Sean: Orla? What's happening?
(growls softly)
(jump scare)
(sinister music)
(high tempo music)
(sudden quiet, light buzzing)
(sinister music)
(groans)
(eerie whispering)
No.
What? (struggles, groans)
No, no, no, no, no.
Uh, oh, God.
No.
(quiet snap)
What the fuck?! What the fuck?!
What the fuck?! (groans)
What the fuck? Wait.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Stop. No, no, no.
Stop, stop. Wait.
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait!
-Wait. No. Wait.
-(teeth gnashing)
-Wait, wait.
-Nora: Get away from him.
What the fuck? Wha...wha...
What the fuck are you doing?
(shotgun clicks)
(cries out)
You can't just tie me
up like this!
Let me go!
(swoosh)
(sinister music)
Is it her?
May...maybe.
Maybe, it's...it's a painting.
Okay? It could be...her, okay?
It could be her, I don't know.
(chair rattles)
What the fuck is going on?
Who is she?
It's not a she.
It's...it's everything.
It's the Dearg Due.
My family has waited generations
for its power to return to us.
I've spent my whole life...
(ominous music)
Who summoned it?
-What the actual fuck
are you talking about?
(shotgun cocks)
Jesus! Wait, fuck, fuck.
Wait, wait.
-Who raised it?
-Erm, what?
-The dolmen.
-Wha...?
The dolmen in the woods.
You went there, didn't you?
-I...
-Who bled?
-Who bled? Eh...
-There has to be blood!
My girlfriend cut her finger!
That's all!
That's all. I don't know.
So, it's chosen.
No.
Not one of you.
Not you.
I will not ever let you
take it from me.
What the fuck is going on?
(struggles, groans, panics)
(panting)
(eerie music)
(screaming)
Uh!
(thud)
Uh...
(heavy breathing)
(door slams shut)
Sean, we're leaving!
(gasping)
Orla: Sean?!
Come on!
We have to get out of here, now!
(sobbing)
(eerie music)
Shit, shit, shit!
(panting)
Oh, no!
(sinister music)
Who's there?
(threatening music)
(snarling)
(vomiting)
Aaaaargh!
Aaargh!
(distant screaming)
(car engine humming)
Lorcan?
Come on, Sean!
(footsteps on gravel)
(whispering, chanting)
(eerie cackling)
(dramatic music)
(panting)
(squelching)
Where is she?
It's gone.
Where?
The woods, I think.
Was it you?
Was it you who bled?
It's a vampire, isn't it?
Orla, what the fuck
is happening?
You can't even comprehend,
can you?
She's not a monster.
She's an angel, fallen
from God's grace and cast out.
But cast out so we can bask
in the gift of her power.
You're fucking crazy.
It's gonna kill all of us.
No. Not me.
The Dearg Due bonded
with one of my ancestors.
The woman you met tonight.
And both of them are
still alive inside of her.
She won't harm me.
She's going to give me
and mine everything.
We tried to summon her.
Rituals.
Sacrifices.
And then you...
you strayed too close.
The Dearg Due can only rise
to find a new host.
She saw something in you.
She means to bond with you next.
No, I don't want it!
Well then, you're a fool!
But don't worry,
you won't get it.
I'm gonna keep this
in the blood.
(thud)
Uh!
(digging)
(snarling)
(chilling music)
(grunting)
Uh...ah!
(eerie music)
(car engine starts)
(engine revving)
(muffled speaking)
Why were you talking
about a vampire?
Ness is dead.
She's dead, Orla.
Is that lady a vampire?
(sinister music)
It was just story, it's a myth.
Myths aren't real.
It, it can't be real.
(haunting music)
I didn't mean it.
I just read it.
(dramatic music intensifies)
(snarling)
(gasping)
(heavy breathing)
No! You're my kin!
(Nora shouting in Irish)
(roaring)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music intensifies)
(roaring)
(gasping)
(haunting music)
(gasping, panting)
Uh!
(frenetic music)
(gasping)
(window pane squeaking)
(roaring)
(frenetic music intensifies)
(snarling, roaring)
(engine starts)
(engine revving)
Get them all!
Sean, we have to turn on
all the lights!
Sean, they're the same
as daylight, okay?
Point one at a window.
Orla: Make sure
you don't change it.
Keep it set to daylight!
(frantic gasping)
(gasping intensifies)
(eerie music)
(phone vibrating)
Orla: Hello, Lorcan?
Oh, thank God.
No, there's no time.
Listen to me.
You have to come and get me
out of here right now.
No, don't come to the house.
I'll sneak out and meet ya
at the gate.
Because we have to leave Sean
behind to keep him busy.
If it has Sean to kill,
it'll give us time to get away.
I don't care. It's exactly what
Nessa would do.
She never really
liked him anyway.
(threatening music)
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay. It's okay.
Orla, help, quick!
-Please help!
-Sean! Be quiet!
Look, the window.
(dramatic music)
(lock clicks)
(lock rattling)
Sean? Sean, what are you doing?
I heard what you said you...
you and Lorcan
were gonna leave me!
Sean? Sean? Sean!
I didn't say anything, okay?
Whatever you heard,
it's not real!
I heard you!
Sean, let me out!
Lorcan isn't even here!
(frantic gasping)
(snarling)
(muffled shouting)
Austin: Awesome job, Ness.
Hold it, hold it, don't move.
That is perfect!
Perfect!
(camera shutting clicking)
Perfect, awesome work, Ness.
Ness: Don't cha know it.
Gorgeous, smile for me. Smile.
You're back.
Of course, we are buddy.
How you doing?
Seanie, my right-hand man!
I told you I couldn't survive
without my Seanie,
my little secret weapon.
Hey, do me a favour, yeah?
-Of course.
-Mix up the lights for me.
We need to get this girl
in technicolour.
-All of them?
-Yeah, buddy.
You know, remember from...
from last time, right?
On the back.
(camera shutter clicking)
I remember.
Hey, Seanie, when you're done
with the lights,
you should come and pose with me
so we can finally start
officially collaborating.
(sinister music)
(camera shutter clicking)
(engine revving)
(panting)
(door banging)
Orla: Sean!
She's making you imagine things!
That's her power!
Sean!
(door banging)
Stunning. Head inside.
You know what we need?
We need a breeze for this dress.
-Like Marilyn?
-Exactly like Marilyn!
Like Marilyn!
Sure thing, Nessa.
(panting)
Uh!
(thudding)
(thud)
(intense music)
(door rumbling)
Sean, no!
(shallow breathing)
Where are they?
Where...where are they?
(threatening music)
(gasping)
(snarling)
Oh, God!
Please don't hurt me.
I'll do anything.
(gasping, sobbing)
Sean: Please...
(sobbing)
Please.
I'll do anything, please!
(sinister music)
(sobbing)
Uh!
(neck cricks)
(sinister music intensifies)
(Sean gasping)
(choking)
(chomping)
(thud)
(panting)
Uh...
(footsteps on gravel)
Austin? Oh, fuck!
It wants this.
It wants Orla too.
(haunting music)
Look what it gave me.
You can't stop it.
It's too powerful to resist.
(vomiting)
(gasping)
(snarling)
(haunting music intensifies)
Uh!
(panting)
Oh, shit!
It's not daylight.
Lorcan: Orla!
Run! Go! Run!
(panting)
(screaming)
(ghoulish screeching)
No, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop, stop! Wait, wait!
(dramatic music)
(panting)
Orla's gonna let it in.
(shallow breathing)
(floorboards creaking)
(switch clicks)
(eerie whispering)
(door slams shut)
(gasping)
(growling)
(snarling)
(shallow breathing)
(eerie growling)
(dramatic music)
(growling)
Dad?
(oozing)
Do you know what it's like...
to be where I am now?
No...you're not real.
Look what you did to me!
It's fake.
(tearing)
Look what you did to me.
Don't hide from it!
No, it's not real.
It's not real.
You know the truth.
You should be dead too!
(dramatic music)
No!
(door slams)
(gasping)
(sobbing)
Fiona: Orla?
No.
You know my voice.
-Mum, please, no.
-Watch.
Watch again.
Watch me burn!
(flames roaring)
No!
(gasping)
(sobbing)
-No!
-Ciara: Orla?
(sobbing)
Where have you been?
You're not real.
You're not here.
Ciara: It was so dark. I...
I couldn't find you.
I looked and looked and looked,
but you weren't there.
No. You're not real.
I am real.
And I found you.
(Orla sobbing)
(mysterious music)
Ciara?
I told you I was here.
I told you I was real.
I finally found you.
I missed you so bad.
Oh, my God, I missed you too!
(sobs) Oh, it's you. It's you.
Why didn't you come with me?
You were supposed
to come with me.
I know. I know I was.
I didn't ask them to save me.
We must be together again.
I'm so sorry.
Please, Orla. Please bring
us back to you.
I can't. I don't know how.
But she said you can.
(sobs) What?
She said you can bring us back.
Who said that?
The lady. She said she can give
you the powers to bring us back.
You just have to want it.
Ciara, I...
Don't you want us back?
No, no. Of course I do!
Then why won't you?
She knows what you want.
What you've craved.
She knows you were too afraid.
There's nothing to fear.
A bond with the Dearg Due
is a death without dying.
Don't you see?
You don't have to face
the darkness.
You'll just be reborn.
What are you doing?
You're meant to join with it.
Let it into you.
Let it take you and you can
join in its power.
What? No, I can't!
-Oh!
-Oh my God...
(squelching)
Don't...
Look at me! Look!
It hurts so much!
Join with the Dearg Due
and use its powers
to bring me back.
No! You're not my sister.
I can't...
It's your fault we died!
Don't. No, don't, please.
Joining with the Dearg Due
is the price you have to pay
for what you did to us!
No, Ciara, you're not my sister.
You're not my sister...
Yes, I am!
No, you're not my sister!
Look at me!
(dramatic music)
My sister...
My sister was good.
My sister loved me.
And my sister would forgive me.
(sobbing)
My sister would forgive me.
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
Uh! Uh...
Please...
(whimpering)
(snarling)
(dramatic music intensifies)
(hissing)
(screaming)
(thud)
(growling)
(panting)
(threatening music)
(footsteps approaching)
(gasps)
(snarling)
(gasping)
You need me to be
a willing host.
That's what Sean said, you need
me to be a willing host.
(grunting)
(growling)
No, please! No, stop!
Please, please! (sobbing)
Stop, please!
Stop! No!
No, please. Please stop.
Please. Please.
(growling)
(sobbing)
You can't make me...
(growling)
No. Please no, no. I don't...
I don't want it.
(sobbing)
(growling)
Uh!
You see?
I'm here. Still me.
I've always been here.
I didn't go away.
You'll still be here too.
And you'll have...everything.
(suspenseful music)
Everything lost
will return to you.
Everything you have
ever dreamed of having...
will be yours.
What are you more afraid of?
Going back to the life
you had before tonight?
Or embracing the life
that could be?
My time is done.
The gift is yours now.
I am ready for the darkness.
Are you?
(sinister music)
(flames roaring)
(groaning)
(thud)
(eerie music)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music intensifies)
(gasps)
(birds chirping)
Ah!
(gasping)
Orla? No, no, no, no, no!
Are you alright? I'm so sorry.
We should have never brought
you out here like this.
I'm gonna look after you, okay?
And whatever you want,
I'll make sure you have it.
(shallow breathing)
What's wrong, Orla?
(vomiting)
Uh!
Aaaargh!
(hissing)
(screaming)
(ripping)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music builds)
Aaaaargh!
(sinister music)
(haunting music)